▍2026 多伦多 WTA1000 第三轮
伊埃拉 6-3 5-7 6-4 麦克纳莉 · 赛后场上采访
Well, Alex is front end here in Toronto
亚历克斯就在多伦多现场
and it is fever pitch atmosphere.
气氛简直沸腾了
The crowd delighted.
观众们也乐开了花
You are through to the round of 16.
你已经打进 1/8 决赛了
Well played.
打得漂亮
A tough match for you this one.
这场对你来说很艰难
Seem to be struggling
你的左脚踝伤
with uh your left ankle.
好像一直在困扰你
Firstly, how are you doing?
你现在感觉怎么样？
I'm okay.
我还好
I um yeah, I think I survived that one.
这场我算是扛过来了
It was so tough.
真的太艰难了
Yeah.
是啊
Um, I want to thank Katie for a great match,
想谢谢凯蒂 打了一场精彩比赛
being a great sport.
她的风度也很好
Um, it's one of those matches
这是那种
that really could have gone either way.
谁赢都不奇怪的比赛
I I think it was really down to details
我觉得最后拼的就是细节
and a little bit of luck.
还有一点运气
So, um, give her her flowers, guys.
把掌声也送给她吧
It was a really great match.
真的是一场精彩的比赛
Clearly a tough win for that one,
那一场确实赢得艰难
but it is your seventh win in a row
但这已经是你的第七连胜
and counting.
而且还在继续
This is some real momentum you're
你现在这股势头
building right now.
是真的很猛
Yeah, I mean these what like two weeks
是啊 这两周
have been incredible for me.
对我来说太不可思议了
just so many extreme emotions
情绪起伏特别大
and and I'm really I'm doing my best
我是真的在尽全力
to to power
想要
through and and be a professional
咬牙撑过去 保持职业
and and do what I know how
做好该做的事情
to do and I mean to play in front
能在你们面前打球
of you guys it's it's amazing.
真的很奇妙
So I mean the motivation to to come here
想到能来这儿
and play another match like
再打一场这样的比赛
it everything just becomes
一切都会
so much more emotional guys like
变得更加动情
Like I don't know,
我也说不好
someone in the crowd said like they wanted
看台上有人说
to be Filipino for tonight and I don't know
今晚想当一次菲律宾人
that I that stuck with me cuz actually I went
这句话一直留在我心里
to like a Bad Bunny concert
因为我看过 Bad Bunny 演唱会
and I felt Puerto Rican for that night.
那晚我觉得自己是波多黎各人
So, I mean, for the Filipino community
所以对菲律宾社群来说
to also have that impact
能带来这样的影响
on on other people, you know,
对别的人也是一样
the Canadians have been so hospitable
加拿大人对我特别友好
to me.
待我很好
They've been amazing these past couple
这几天他们
of days.
一直都很棒
So, um I really hope that, you know,
所以我也希望
the Canadians also get
加拿大人也能感受到
that feeling of hospit hospitality, sorry,
那种款待的感觉 抱歉
from the Filipinos.
来自菲律宾人
Yeah.
是啊
Listen, we're going to let you get some rest,
好了 让你去休息吧
folks.
各位
But one last time this evening,
但今晚最后一次
give it up for Alexandra Eala.
掌声送给伊埃拉